Naughty girls go to hell... Really naughty girls conquer it.
Lady Death is a fantasy, animation, horror film directed by Andy Orjuela.
When accused by the townspeople of being in league with the Devil,
Hope finds herself in a satanic deal for her life.
After refusing the terms of the deal, she transforms into the powerful Lady
Death and vows to wrest control of hell from her father.
Lady Death / Hope (voice), played by Christine McPeters Auten.
Lucifer / Matthias (voice), played by Mike Kleinhenz.
Pagan (voice), played by Andy McAvin.
Cremator (voice), played by Rob Mungle.
Asmodeus / Large Torture Troll (voice), played by Mike MacRae.
Niccolo (voice), played by Chris Patton.
Lady Death is a fictional goddess appearing in American
comic books published by Coffin Comics.
Created by Brian Pulido, Lady Death first appeared in
Eternity Comics' Evil Ernie #1 in December 1991.
Lady Death then reappeared in the Evil Ernie: The Resurrection miniseries
published by Pulido under his now-defunct company Chaos!
Comics in 1994.
The character was also the subject of a full-length animated
feature film released in July 2004 by ADV Films.
Incarnations of the character have been illustrated by such comic book artists as
Steven Hughes, Mike Deodato, Romano Molenaar, Dheeraj Verma and Ivan Reis.
Brian Pulido has optioned publishing licenses through various
independent companies such as CrossGen Comics and Avatar Press.
As of 2024, Lady Death was published by Pulido's Coffin Comics.
By 2017, the comic had sold 15 million copies in seven languages.
In addition, Lady Death has been depicted in artworks by a number of well-known fantasy artists
such as Dorian Cleavenger, Gerald Brom, Boris Vallejo, Joe Jusko and Julie Bell.
The film explores themes of satan, breast, lucifer, demon, adult animation.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.